very good you play do it make sure
很好，你玩狗屎，请确保
good morning everyone welcome you're the
大家早上好欢迎您
most organized audience I've ever seen
我见过的最有组织的观众
you like shuffled out made space for
您喜欢改组腾出的空间
everyone using up all the seats it's
每个人都用光了
fantastic I've never seen that before
太棒了，我从未见过
and I've been to a bunch of conferences
我去过很多会议
well done and yes hi I'm Tricia I mean
做得好，是的，我是特里西娅，我的意思是
want to serve you when I know about Java
我想在Java方面为您服务
and I intend home this isn't alarming at
我打算回家这并不令人震惊
all and I'm a technical advocate for
所有人，我是
JetBrains I work mostly with IntelliJ
我主要与IntelliJ合作的JetBrains
IDEA anyone using IntelliJ IDEA all of
任何使用IntelliJ IDEA的人
you I love you all your fantastic an
你我爱你你所有的幻想
eclipse users and so sorry for you and I
蚀用户，为您和我感到抱歉
also work with up source the code review
也可以与源代码一起进行代码审查
tool but most of my job is kind of doing
工具，但我的大部分工作是在做
and research into what's coming in Java
并研究Java的新功能
or what's kind of currently interesting
或当前有趣的是什么
in Java and then say going out how to
在Java中，然后说出如何
apply it to to kind of your day job
应用于日常工作
basically because I was a Java program
基本上是因为我是Java程序
for about 20 years and that's quite
大约20年了
frightening and and you know people
令人恐惧，你认识的人
always tell you about new and exciting
总是告诉你新的和令人兴奋的
stuff but that's not so relevant to what
的东西，但这与什么无关
you're doing in the day job unless
你在做日常工作，除非
someone makes it more applicable to you
有人让它更适合您
so that's kind of how I see my job if
所以这就是我对工作的看法
you like so today we're going to talk
你喜欢所以今天我们要谈
about real world Java 9 and which is
关于现实世界中的Java 9，这是
great because Java 9 isn't out yet what
很棒，因为Java 9还没有推出
I really want to cover is a little bit
我真的很想掩饰一点
of jigsaw in action and who went to one
拼图在行动中，谁去了
or both of Marc's sessions at the
或Marc在
conference that's great because I don't
会议很棒，因为我不
want to repeat a lot of the stuff that
想重复很多东西
he said I just want to give us a
他说我只想给我们一个
high-level look at using jigsaw I'm
我用拼图看了一下
going to cover a bit about reactive
会涉及一些反应性
programming in Java 9 of I'll hide mark
Java 9中的编程我会隐藏标记
is in my audience please don't shout at
在我的观众中，请不要对
me if I get it wrong and and I also what
我如果我弄错了，我也
I really really want to do and hopefully
我真的很想做，希望
I'll have time is at the end a good
我有时间最后会很好
chunk of time we'll be going over all
我们将花费大量时间
the other features in Java 9 well not
Java 9中的其他功能不是
all of them but the ones that I think
所有这些，但我认为
are going to be relevant to you in your
在您中与您息息相关
day job so they're kind of interesting
日常工作，所以他们很有趣
stuff to others as developers firstly
首先向开发人员介绍其他东西
let's step back and take a look at why
让我们退后一步，看看为什么
we care about Java 9 other than it's new
除了新版本，我们还关心Java 9
and exciting and obviously we want new
令人兴奋的，显然我们想要新的
and exciting from my understanding and
从我的理解中令人兴奋，
of course you have to bear in mind that
当然你要记住
no one I hope no one is using in
没有人希望没有人使用
production yet the idea of Java 9 is
生产但Java 9的想法是
you'll get a bunch of stuff
你会得到一堆东西
three you'll get better performance
三，您将获得更好的性能
better use of memory it uses new CPU
更好地使用内存，它使用新的CPU
instructions things like that so you
指示类似的事情，所以你
should get things like performance
应该得到性能
improvements and generally a better
改善和总体上更好
experience from things like the compiler
编译器之类的经验
and without having to use any of the new
并且无需使用任何新
features so this is a good thing let's
功能，这是一件好事，让我们
like let's look at the elephant in the
就像让我们看一下大象
room straight away and most people when
房间马上和大多数人
they talk about Java 9 they kind of that
他们谈论Java 9
I mentioned jigsaw and particularly if
我提到了拼图，特别是如果
your name is mark Reinhold and and so
你的名字是马克·莱因霍尔德（Mark Reinhold）等
this is kind of a big feature for Java 9
这是Java 9的一大功能
and well I don't know I was going to say
好吧，我不知道我要说什么
it's perhaps not super exciting to us as
对于我们来说，这可能并不令人兴奋
developers maybe maybe we'll get onto
开发人员，也许我们会继续
that so you hear about Java 9 you might
这样您就可以了解Java 9
hear about the repple who's heard of the
听说谁听说过
repple Jay shell fantastic audience you
重复杰伊壳梦幻般的观众你
are and so maybe more than half of you
是的，所以也许你们一半以上
so the idea of the reporter who's used a
所以记者的想法
rattle in another language that isn't
用另一种不是
Java I don't know if that's the same set
Java我不知道那是同一套
of people but it's a good chunk of you
的人，但这是你们的很大一部分
so most of us who've been doing Java and
所以我们大多数人都在从事Java和
only Java for a long time the repple is
很长时间以来，只有Java是
kind of an interesting and new idea the
一种有趣而新颖的想法
idea of being able to execute small
能够执行小事的想法
snippets of code from the command line
命令行中的代码片段
and try stuff out this is quite good for
尝试一下，这对于
introducing yourself to the language but
介绍自己的语言，但
it's also quite good for like trying out
它也很适合尝试
bits and pieces to see how things work
点点滴滴看看事情如何运作
and I think this is this is an
我认为这是一个
interesting idea Java because in the
Java很有趣，因为在
past you know we're accused of having
过去你知道我们被指控拥有
quite a lot of boilerplate I don't know
我不知道很多样板
why they're saying that when a simple
为什么他们这么说，当一个简单的
hello world application is only 24 lines
你好世界申请只有24行
of code but the record will help us and
代码，但记录将帮助我们和
try stuff out without having to have all
尝试所有东西而不必拥有所有东西
of that boilerplate but we're kind of
样板，但我们有点
left with this question of oK we've got
剩下的这个问题，我们有
the rattle and jigsaw what else is there
拨浪鼓和拼图，还有什么
is there anything that's kind of
有什么东西可以
interesting for me as a developer but it
作为开发人员对我来说很有趣，但是
turns out like in Java 9 there's one or
事实证明，在Java 9中有一个或
two things going into the into the
两件事进入了
language some of these aren't
语言中的一些不是
necessarily going to be visible to you
一定对你可见
as developers there's a lot of stuff
作为开发人员，有很多东西
that's gone onto the covers obviously
显然已经被掩盖了
the things like modularization of the
诸如模块化的东西
JDK there's things like update is
JDK就像更新是
logging inside the JDK things like I
在JDK中记录类似我的东西
think I wrote a bunch of performance
认为我写了很多表演
tests and stuff like that so that's not
测试之类的东西，所以不是
necessarily visible to you but you
必须对您可见，但您
should benefit from it in terms of it
应该从中受益
being a better written better design
做一个更好的书面更好的设计
language but there are some other bits
语言，但还有其他一些地方
and pieces in here that I want to take a
在这里，我想拿一个
look at at the end as well the end may
也要看最后
be all that a third of the way through
做到三分之一
the through the presentations
通过演示
which things in there might be most
里面哪些东西最多
applicable to us as usual I like to set
适用于我们平时喜欢的设置
my expectations for this talk
我对这次演讲的期望
appropriately low since there are about
适当低，因为大约
500 of you in this room and of course
当然有500个人在这个房间里
you should not be using Java 9 in
您不应该在其中使用Java 9
production please don't do that it's not
生产请不要这样做，不是
ready yet and it does change from week
准备好了，它确实从星期开始改变
to week so it's um you know every time
一周，所以每次你都知道
you download the latest version there
您在那里下载最新版本
are some changes in the way things work
事物运作方式有一些变化
so don't use it in production but do
所以不要在生产中使用它
have a play with it definitely it's
玩的肯定是
ready for for trying out
准备尝试
speaking of which everything is early
说什么都早
access so again setting expectations
再次访问以设定期望
appropriately low I'm using an early
适当低，我正在使用早期
access version of Java 9 I'm actually
我实际上是访问Java 9的版本
using build 1 6 6 I think the most
我认为使用构建1 6 6
recent one is build 1 6 8 but we'll
最近的一个是build 1 6 8，但我们会
build 1 6 8 doesn't play nicely with
版本1 6 8与
most recent EA build of IntelliJ IDEA so
最新的IntelliJ IDEA EA版本
you have to get sort of the right
你必须得到正确的选择
combinations of the early access things
抢先体验组合
in order to try and try and get things
为了尝试并尝试得到东西
to work properly so I'm using only
正常工作，所以我只使用
access Java 9 and then the early access
访问Java 9，然后进行早期访问
builders IntelliJ IDEA and 2017 point to
建筑商IntelliJ IDEA和2017指向
which the early access only came out
那些早期访问只是出来的
like last week so it's in very early
就像上周一样，现在还很早
days I won't use the word unstable but
几天我不会用不稳定这个词，而是
also it's always interesting and of
而且总是很有趣的
course with Java 9 we really don't know
Java 9当然我们真的不知道
what best practice looks like yet and
最佳做法是什么样的
because we're not using it we're not
因为我们没有使用它，所以我们没有
using in production we're only just
在生产中使用我们只是
starting to get an idea of what best
开始了解什么是最好的
practice might look like in terms of
实践可能看起来像
Java 8 with lambdas and streams and
带有lambda和流的Java 8
things so I can't really tell you like
事情，所以我真的不能告诉你喜欢
this is the way to do stuff jigsaw wise
这是做拼图明智的方法
because we won't really know that until
因为我们直到那时才会真正知道
it's embedded in and people start using
它被嵌入并且人们开始使用
it a lot more in anger if you like let
如果你愿意的话，会更生气
me set the background for the case study
我为案例研究设定了背景
we're going to look at and at devoxx UK
我们将看看devoxx UK
a couple of years ago I did a demo Java
几年前，我做了一个Java演示
8 in anger I wrote this application to
8我很生气地写了这个申请
demonstrate Java 8 features like lambdas
演示Java 8功能，例如lambdas
and streams and the idea is it's a Java
和流，想法是它是Java
effects UI with which responds to
响应的效果UI
real-time tweet data so and it also
实时推文数据等等
happens to be architected with lots of
恰好有很多
tiny services that might be micro sized
可能很小的微小服务
but they're not micro services because
但它们不是微服务，因为
they're not reliable they fall over all
他们不可靠，他们跌倒了
the time there's no monitoring or any de
没有监控或没有任何时间的时候
stuff is actually appropriate to micro
东西实际上适合微
services but the idea of this
服务，但是这个主意
application is to was to use
应用是要使用
eight features to architect something
架构某些东西的八个功能
which is kind of running as lots of
这就像很多
independent services and react to
独立服务并对
real-time data and it turns out that
实时数据，事实证明
this is quite a good example to use with
这是一个很好的例子
Java nine particularly when we're
Java 9特别是当我们
looking at things like the rector
看着像导演
streams API which is something I want to
流API，这是我想要的
go into in a little bit of detail if
详细一点，如果
you're interested in the original
您对原版感兴趣
application and I've got resources for
应用程序，我有资源
that specifically so I'm not going to go
明确地说，所以我不会去
into all the ins and outs of what it
进入它的所有来龙去脉
does and why it does it because I
以及为什么这样做，因为我
already have a presentation on that so
已经有一个演讲了
first and foremost by the way I've only
首先，也是我唯一的方式
got like 50 minutes to talk about all of
大概有50分钟的时间谈论所有
Java 9 so I'm going to talk quite fast I
Java 9，所以我要讲得很快
do apologize but I'm in London so I feel
道歉但我在伦敦所以我感到
comfortable doing that here and next up
舒适地在这里和下一个
yes so I think probably if you read
是的，所以我想，如果您阅读
anything about Java 9 if you read stuff
如果您阅读过有关Java 9的任何内容
in the news you might get a little bit
在新闻中你可能会得到一点
alarmed by some of the scare stories of
惊恐的一些恐怖故事
everything is going to break them Java 9
一切都会破坏它们Java 9
so the first thing I really wanted to do
所以我真正想做的第一件事
is take an application like my
是像我这样的应用程序
application it's small ish as in small
应用程序很小，就像小
enough to get your brain around it but
足以让您的大脑绕开它，但是
complicated enough to do something
足以做某事的复杂
interesting and I want to compile it
有趣，我想编译它
with Java 9 and see what breaks and that
Java 9，看看有什么坏处
way we can get an idea of what potential
我们可以了解潜在潜力的方式
problems might exist so let's try and
问题可能存在，所以让我们尝试
get this run in oh yeah the first thing
让这个运行哦，是的，第一件事
I want to do is I want to see it running
我想做的是我想看到它正在运行
at the beginning just to make sure that
一开始只是为了确保
everything's working to begin with
一切都从一开始
because if it doesn't if it doesn't work
因为如果不行不通
before I start refactoring it's Java 9
在我开始重构之前是Java 9
there's zero hope to the rest user of
其余用户对零希望
the rest of the demo
其余的演示
so as I said this runs as a series of
正如我所说的那样，
independent services I've got one
我有一个独立的服务
service which kind of acts as a Twitter
服务像Twitter一样
service it's reading tweets from a file
服务，它正在从文件中读取推文
to make life a bit easier I've got one
为了让生活更轻松一点
service which is extracting the username
正在提取用户名的服务
from those tweets I have a mood service
从那些推文中，我有心情服务
which is not starting let's try that
这还没有开始，让我们尝试一下
again I have a mood service which looks
我又有一个情绪服务，看起来
at the tweets and extracts whether the
在推文上，提取是否
tweet is generally happy or generally
推文通常是快乐的
sad and I have a dashboard which is
悲伤，我有一个仪表板
showing me those results in real time
实时显示这些结果
yeah look at that an exception
是的，看看那个例外
straightaway I think it's because I
我认为这是因为我
started the dashboard before I started
开始之前先启动了仪表板
the mood service hence my comment about
情绪服务，因此我对
lack of reliability
缺乏可靠性
it's kind of working
这是一种工作
[Music]
[音乐]
all right there we go so yes so it works
好的，我们去了，是的，所以工作
before a refactor it's that's a really
在重构之前，这是一个真正的
good start and right now I'm going to
好的开始，现在我要
see what happened the first time I
看看我第一次发生了什么
compiled this application against Java 9
针对Java 9编译了此应用程序
it was obviously a Java 8 application so
这显然是一个Java 8应用程序，所以
let's take it back to a version which
让我们回到一个版本
before I started doing the Java 9
在我开始做Java 9之前
migration
移民
so if I build this
所以如果我建立这个
there we go so there's a few things I
我们去那里，所以我有几件事
did insert a couple of things to fail on
确实插入了一些失败的内容
purpose but most of the stuff that
目的，但大多数东西
failed was already there firstly you
失败首先已经存在
can't have underscore as a valid field
下划线不能为有效字段
name now people might think I didn't
现在命名人们可能会认为我没有
know you could do that that looks
知道你可以那样做
exciting I can use underscore as a valid
令人兴奋的是我可以使用下划线作为有效
field name and up until Java eight you
字段名称，直到Java 8
could use underscores the valid field or
可以在有效字段中使用下划线或
parameter or variable name but in Java
参数或变量名称，但使用Java
nine in Java eight you'll get a warning
Java 8中的9点，您会收到警告
in Java nine and it's not going to work
在Java 9中无法正常工作
anymore so don't do that there's a
不再这样做了
fairly easy fix and something sensible
相当容易的修复和明智的选择
and away you go and the reason being
然后你走了，原因是
they're going to use underscore or
他们将使用下划线或
something interesting in later versions
在以后的版本中有趣的事情
of Java so that's kind of cool but in
Java的，所以有点酷，但是
the meantime obviously we have to get
同时显然我们必须得到
rid of it from our code bases one of the
从我们的代码库中删除它之一
other things is to take it out of
其他的就是把它拿出来
presentation mode so of course as we
演示模式，当然就像我们
always here with jigsaw that one of the
总是在这里与拼图，其中之一
ideas was to encapsulate the internal
想法是封装内部
API is you shouldn't be accessing
API是您不应该访问的
anything which is like some misc and I
任何像杂项的东西，我
wrote this application knowing I
知道我写了这个应用程序
shouldn't access some doc miss but being
不应该访问一些文档错过但
too lazy to figure out what the right
懒得弄清楚对不对
way to do it was so I was using the
这样做的方式是，所以我正在使用
encoder and now under Java 9 of course
编码器，现在当然在Java 9下
it doesn't compile and this fix times
它无法编译，并且此修复时间
actually fairly easy because there's a
实际上相当容易，因为有一个
there's a simple replacement for this so
有一个简单的替代品，所以
here instead of using my basic C for
在这里而不是使用我的基本C
encoder I use a base64 very 64 Java util
编码器，我使用base64非常64 Java util
get encoder and code two strings so I
得到编码器并编码两个字符串，所以我
can just replace that and then
可以取代它，然后
everything compiles if I build
如果我建立，一切都会编译
everything now
现在一切
my whole application compiled
我的整个应用程序已编译
successfully so for me it was fairly
成功，所以对我来说，这相当
painless to convert this Java eight
轻松转换此Java八
application to use Java 9 without using
应用程序以不使用Java 9
any of the new features there were some
任何新功能都有一些
problems but nothing nothing to
问题，但没什么可
showstopping so that's not as bad as I
表现一流，所以还不如我
thought it would be what do I do with my
以为那是我该怎么办
remote who is and so when I created this
远程是谁，所以当我创建这个
presentation I didn't actually want to
我实际上不想要的演示文稿
talk about jigsaw at all because for
完全谈论拼图，因为
start there going to be lots of people
开始会有很多人
doing talks about jigsaw it's going to
做关于拼图的讨论
be the focus of sort of a lot of the
是很多的重点
Java Nayan presentations and it's quite
Java Nayan演示文稿，相当
a big topic you can't just kind of
一个大话题，你不能只是
mention oh and by the way jigsaw but it
提哦，顺便说一下，但它
turned out that I ended up playing with
原来我最终和
jigsaw anyway to figure out like how
拼图还是想办法
it's going to look for me in a fairly
它会相当公平地寻找我
small project but also mainly because
小项目，也主要是因为
Gradle doesn't work with Java 9 at the
Gradle在Java 9上不起作用
moment and I heard this week on Monday I
此刻，我在本周星期一听到我
did get it to work with Java 9 with a
确实使其与Java 9一起使用
bunch of like compiler flags and I have
一堆类似的编译器标志，我有
to run it without the daemon and had to
在没有守护程序的情况下运行它，并且不得不
run it in the command line I couldn't
我无法在命令行中运行它
run it from inside IntelliJ and there
从IntelliJ内部运行它
are some things you can do to get Gradle
您可以做一些事情来获得Gradle
to work but I could not get my project
工作，但我无法完成我的项目
to work inside IntelliJ with Gradle in a
与Gradle一起在IntelliJ中工作
multi module project and the whole point
多模块项目和整个要点
was this is a multi module project so
这是一个多模块项目吗
you know I kind of wanted Gradle to work
你知道我想要Gradle工作
but it also means that I can perhaps
但这也意味着我也许
start playing with modules so what I did
开始玩模块，所以我做了
was so the directory structure we've got
原来是这样的目录结构
here is a fairly typical Gradle type
这是一个非常典型的Gradle类型
directory structure where I have I've
我所拥有的目录结构
got a laser on this that's really silly
真的很傻
so I've got a couple of different
所以我有几个不同
modules and the modules have got source
模块和模块有来源
main Java source tests Java inside it's
Java的主要源代码在其中测试Java
a fairly typical groovy and Gradle
相当典型的常规和Gradle
structure what I ended up doing when I
整理我最终做的事
started playing with with jigsaw I
开始玩拼图游戏
changed the structure of my project to
将我的项目的结构更改为
follow more closely what it's suggested
更仔细地遵循建议
in the tutorials and here that meant I
在教程中，这意味着我
had source and then all of my individual
有资料，然后我所有的人
modules inside my source territory and
我的来源区域内的模块
test and all my individual modules aside
测试和我所有的个人模块
my test directory which is kind of
我的测试目录是
inside out from what I had before
由内而外
and this mirrors what's inside the open
这反映了开放中的内容
JDK so I kind of wanted to follow that
JDK，所以我有点想遵循
this was a non-trivial thing to do to
这是一件不平凡的事情
rearrange your whole thing just so that
重新整理整个内容，以便
you can put some module info files
你可以放一些模块信息文件
inside your modules I have got it to
在您的模块内部，我已经知道了
work with the Gradle structure as well
也可以使用Gradle结构
so it's not a mandatory part but if
所以这不是必须的部分，但是如果
you're following their tutorials you'll
您将按照他们的教程进行操作
see a directory structure which is
看到一个目录结构是
different to what you're used to it's
与您习惯的不同
different to the sort of groovy way of
与那种古怪的方式不同
doing those Gradle way of doing stuff so
做那些Gradle做事的方式
in my production code I've added a
在生产代码中，我添加了一个
module inside of Java magic incantation
Java魔咒内部的模块
file into each of my individual modules
归档到我的各个模块中
you'll notice I don't have them in my
你会注意到我没有他们
test directory and this was a pragmatic
测试目录，这是一个务实的
choice someone call it hack a pragmatic
选择有人称它为务实
choice to get everything working inside
选择让所有东西都在里面的选择
IntelliJ IDEA and because you can't
IntelliJ IDEA，因为您不能
obviously you can't have modules for the
显然，您无法为
same package names in two different
相同的软件包名称（两个不同）
modules so I can't have a test module
模块，所以我没有测试模块
and a production module and so I know
和生产模块，所以我知道
there is a way around that using jigsaw
有一种解决方法，可以使用拼图
but I didn't have the time to get that
但我没有时间去做
working so I chose this as a pragmatic
工作，所以我选择这是一个务实的
approach for the demo there are of
演示的方法有
course and trade-offs of this in that
的过程和权衡
for example I can only run the tests
例如我只能运行测试
from inside the IDE also because I'm not
从IDE内部也因为我不是
using Gradle anymore I also manage my
不再使用Gradle我也可以管理我的
dependencies from inside the IDE so this
从IDE内部的依赖关系，所以这
is not really a production rating system
并不是真正的生产评级系统
as it stands right now but what it did
就目前而言，但它做了什么
find when I was doing this whole process
找出我何时完成整个过程
of modularizing my code is my original
我的代码模块化是我的原始
module structure was kind of naive shall
模块结构有点天真
we say so I had them I've got two
我们说，所以我有他们，我有两个
back-end services and the code for the
后端服务和代码
back-end services depended upon the code
后端服务取决于代码
for my Twitter service now that doesn't
现在我的Twitter服务没有
make any sense I can listen to the
我可以听的任何意义
Twitter service but I shouldn't be
Twitter服务，但我不应该
dependent upon the code in the Twitter
取决于Twitter中的代码
service so by looking at my dependency
服务，所以通过看我的依赖
structure by looking at modules as a
通过将模块视为一个结构
sort of first-class citizen I realized I
我意识到我是一流的公民
kind of modeled my model modification
模仿了我的模型修改
incorrectly I also noticed that the
错误地，我还注意到
client code was dependent on the web
客户代码取决于网络
sockets API but nothing else was which
套接字API，但没有别的是
is kind of weird because they're all
有点奇怪，因为它们都是
using WebSockets and my reactor streams
使用WebSockets和我的反应堆流
API was being used by two of my modules
我的两个模块正在使用API
rather than either all of them or just
而不是全部或全部
one which manages the API side of stuff
一个管理东西的API方面
so I kind of had a bit of noise in there
所以我有点吵
which just it just felt a bit wrong the
只是感觉有点不对
way that the code had been organized so
代码的组织方式
when I was thinking about what my
当我在想我的
modules really were and how to
模块真的是，以及如何
encapsulate the code what my
封装代码我的
dependencies should really look like I
依赖关系应该看起来像我
rearranged a lot of this so now all my
重新安排了很多，所以现在我所有的
services are kind of at the same level
服务在同一级别
they don't depend upon each other code
他们不依赖彼此的代码
wise so that feels much more correct and
明智的做法会感觉更正确，
I have a module which is this reusable
我有一个可重用的模块
service code which is dependent upon by
服务代码取决于
all the services that make sense - and
所有有意义的服务-和
this is the only one that cares about
这是唯一在乎的
WebSockets because this is a thing which
WebSockets，因为这是
hides away the implementation which
隐藏了哪些实现
happens to be WebSockets from the actual
恰好是实际的WebSockets
services themselves I also have all the
服务本身，我也有所有
back-end services dependent upon my
后端服务取决于我
helper module for the reactive streams
反应性流的辅助模块
API so that's cool because they all use
API，所以很酷，因为它们都使用
reactive streams and then I have two
反应性流，然后我有两个
services which use rxjava by choice and
通过选择使用rxjava的服务和
one service which uses reactor because I
一种使用反应堆的服务，因为我
wanted to show that you can use
想表明你可以使用
different implementations of the of the
的不同实现
reactor streams API which we'll look at
我们将看的反应堆流API
later on so I was much happier with this
后来，所以我对此更加满意
module structure and by thinking about
模块结构以及通过思考
modularity and thinking about my
模块化和对我的思考
dependencies I came up with a much
我想出了很多依赖
cleaner design for my application so
更清洁的设计，适合我的应用
let's take a look at what was involved
让我们看看所涉及的
with creating a module info file and
创建模块信息文件
what that sort of means and I know mark
这种方式是什么，我知道吗
covered this in his talk this morning
今天早上在他的演讲中谈到了这一点
but I'm going to do it from inside the
但我将从内部进行
IDE because that's what we really do in
IDE，因为这就是我们真正要做的
the real world all RIT was really
在现实世界中，所有RIT都是
impressed with with Mark's command line
对Mark的命令行印象深刻
foo just I just don't work that way cool
foo我只是不那么酷
all right so let's switch to the right
好吧，让我们切换到右边
branch
科
okay so you can see here I've got my
好吧，所以你可以在这里看到我有我的
supply modules let's put this in because
供应模块，我们把它放进去是因为
he's a bit better and what I've got is
他好一点了，我所拥有的是
in most of my modules I have the module
在我的大多数模块中，我都有模块
info file I have a module which I
信息文件，我有一个模块
haven't converted into being a jigsaw
还没变成拼图
module yet so what I need to do is I
模块，所以我需要做的是
need to create a new module info
需要创建一个新的模块信息
IntelliJ makes a reasonable guess as to
IntelliJ对
what the name of that module should be
该模块的名称应为
and I'd like to keep it like that you
我想像你一样
can't really see that very well and so
真的不能很好看，所以
by doing that by adding my module info
通过添加我的模块信息来做到这一点
Java for this particular module and I
这个特定模块的Java和我
start to magically use things like
开始神奇地使用诸如
module paths and I'm doing things the
模块路径，我正在做的事情
modular way rather than the old way
模块化的方式，而不是旧的方式
which is the way that we're doing it
这就是我们这样做的方式
right now so now when I compile it I
现在，所以现在当我编译它时
should get some interesting errors
应该会出现一些有趣的错误
and what we see is inside this module
而我们所看到的是该模块内部
one of the classes now which was
现在的课程之一是
compiling fine before now it says the
之前还可以编译，它说
module sensitive flow does not have the
模块敏感流没有
module Java logging in requirements
模块Java登录要求
obviously because I'm using IntelliJ
显然是因为我正在使用IntelliJ
IDEA I use alt enter to magically fix my
我使用Alt Enter神奇地修复了我的想法
problem and what we see is module info
问题，我们看到的是模块信息
now we have requires Java dot logging so
现在我们需要Java点记录
by default it's going to is going to be
默认情况下它将是
able to see everything from Java dot
能够从Java点看到所有内容
base but not all of the other modules
基本但不是所有其他模块
inside the JDK so you you have to go in
在JDK中，因此您必须进入
and declare which of the modules you
并声明您使用哪个模块
need to use you can do that either by
需要使用，您可以通过
Auto fixing stuff or obviously you get
自动修复东西，或者显然得到
some nice happy code completion for all
所有人都满意的代码完成
of your Java modules them so now that
您的Java模块对其进行了
that's not erroring what's our next
这没有错我们的下一个
error so we have a similar problem here
错误，所以我们在这里有一个类似的问题
only this isn't from inside the JDK this
只是这不是来自JDK内部
is an external and external dependency
是外部和外部依赖
on an XML jar file I need to add that
在XML jar文件上，我需要添加
library to the cluster idea and then I
库到集群的想法，然后我
need to say add requires reactive dot
需要说添加需要反应点
streams to module info so do the same
流到模块信息，因此执行相同操作
sort of thing we have now we have two
我们现在有两种东西
different requires one from inside the
不同需要从内部
JDK and one which is using automatic
JDK和一种正在使用自动
modules so it's going to use the
模块，因此它将使用
external jar file there and then those
外部的jar文件，然后那些
errors go away what's our next set of
错误消失了，我们的下一套是什么
errors
错误
now from outside from a different module
现在从外面从另一个模块
I get error is sensitive flow does not
我得到的错误是敏感流程没有
export the package since the flow to the
将包从流中导出到
module sensor user so now this is
模块传感器用户，所以现在这是
complaining about the fact that some
抱怨一些人
external module is using something from
外部模块正在使用
inside this module so this module needs
在此模块内部，因此该模块需要
to declare what some what other modules
声明其他一些模块
can use so I'm just going to export my
可以使用，所以我只是要导出我的
package there and then everything should
包装在那里，然后一切都应该
just work so that's kind of fine and
只是工作，所以很好，
that's that's okay for a small little
一点点就可以了
module like this there's not much going
像这样的模块没有太多的事情
on in there there's a requires and
里面有一个需求
exports and that could fairly easily be
出口，这很容易做到
fixed up by addressing each error by
通过解决每个错误来解决
error
错误
I'll show you some of my other module
我将向您展示其他模块
infos which cost me slightly more to do
花费了我更多时间的信息
so this is the UI here you can see that
所以这是UI，您可以看到
I require a bunch of the Java effects
我需要一堆Java效果
modules and Java
模块和Java
logging and I also JavaFX uses
日志记录，我也使用JavaFX
reflection so I had to open up my pretty
反思，所以我不得不打开我的漂亮
much all of my code to Java effects for
我的所有代码都对Java有影响
reflection now i explicitly decided to
反思现在我明确决定
just open it just to java effects and I
只需将其打开以使用Java效果，我
want to open it to everything to be able
想要向所有人开放
to access me and I also have to export
访问我，我也必须导出
this is an interesting a lot of these
这些很有趣
kind of came up as errors while I was
当时我是作为错误出现的
compiling and while I was running stuff
编译，而我正在运行的东西
so I was just kind of like hacking away
所以我有点像在偷东西
to try and get it to work and it turns
尝试使其工作，它变成
out that when I showed this to someone
当我向某人展示这个
from inside Oracle I shouldn't have to
从Oracle内部，我不必
do that and there's actually a bug arose
这样做，实际上出现了一个错误
within the JDK as to how they're going
在JDK中如何进行
to address this so this is the way that
解决这个问题，这就是
Java if X happens to do its reflection
如果X恰好反映了Java
over your code but that's the magic
在您的代码上，但这就是魔术
incantation I needed and that all works
我需要的咒语，所有的作品
another one and let's look at service
另一个，让我们看看服务
this one uses a whole bunch of stuff
这个用了一堆东西
from external jar file so a lot of these
从外部的jar文件中，所以很多
are automatic modules and I found this
是自动模块，我发现了这个
by trial and error brute force because
通过反复试验的蛮力，因为
I'm stubborn but I would suggest you use
我很固执，但我建议您使用
that you read the documentation for the
您阅读了有关
Jade X 2 land use hatch because it takes
Jade X 2土地使用舱口盖，因为它需要
way less time than restarting your
比重新启动您的时间更少的时间
application all the time and figuring
一直在申请和确定
out what these errors mean so yeah
找出这些错误是什么意思，是的
do read the manual it's very useful so
请务必阅读手册，它非常有用，因此
that's what that's what I have to do to
那就是我要做的
kind of get my application to be more
有点让我的申请变得更多
modular it is a small education it's not
模块化，这不是一个小小的教育
like this massive enterprise
像这个庞大的企业
applications it took me about a day a
申请花了我大约一天的时间
day and a half to get that all running
一天半的时间使所有运行
and working the the pain I found was
而努力，我发现的痛苦是
mostly the fact that I am greater
主要是我更大
doesn't work I spent another day this
不起作用，我花了另一天时间
week trying to get Gradle to work so
一周尝试让Gradle工作
great doesn't work with Java 9 right now
great不适用于Java 9
I'm not sure about the state of maven
我不确定行家的状态
that's I think that works under certain
我认为在某些情况下
circumstances I think Gradle works if
我认为Gradle的工作原理是
you don't have a multi module project
您没有多模块项目
but kind of a lot of us are working with
但是我们很多人正在与
multi module projects and if you decide
多模块项目，如果您决定
to reorganize the file structure that's
重新整理文件结构
a non-trivial task I would not recommend
我不推荐一项非平凡的任务
doing it unless you absolutely have to
除非您绝对必须这样做
and of course the way that I've got this
当然我有这个方法
to work is there's no command-line build
工作没有命令行构建
for this there's no way of running the
为此，无法运行
test inside a CI environment or
在CI环境中测试或
something like that one of the other
类似的东西
pains is that the IDE support there is
麻烦的是那里有IDE支持
either a support for things like jigsaw
对拼图之类的东西的支持
as and so I've got some auto-completion
就这样，我有一些自动完成
i've got some quick fixes I have some
我有一些快速修复方法
help there from the IDE but I don't have
从IDE那里帮忙，但我没有
like a magic generate me my module info
像魔术一样为我生成了我的模块信息
type button I don't have some of the
键入按钮，我没有一些
other things which might make my life a
其他可能使我的生活变得美好的事物
little bit easier I don't get quick
一点点容易，我就不快
fixes for everything so we are working
修复了所有问题，因此我们正在努力
on that but what we what we need from
在那之上，但是我们需要什么
the JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA side is that
JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA方面是
if you find pain working with Java 9 in
如果您发现使用Java 9感到痛苦
IntelliJ IDEA we need you to report that
IntelliJ IDEA我们需要您报告
to us so that we can fix it basically
给我们，以便我们可以基本上解决它
and do do your homework if you're going
如果你要去做功课
to do this particularly jigsaw do do a
为此特别是拼图做一个
lot of reading figure out how the tools
很多阅读都弄清楚了工具是如何
work figure out how the stuff works from
弄清楚这些东西是如何工作的
the command line before diving into the
在跳入命令行之前
IDE because otherwise you don't really
IDE，因为否则您不是真的
understand what's going on underneath
了解下面发生了什么
the covers and it can be quite painful
封面，这可能会很痛苦
right I want to move on and talk about
对，我想继续谈论
the reactive API because this whole talk
反应性API，因为整个讨论
was supposed to be about rah reactive is
本来是关于rah反应的
good and and here's OD reactive in Java
很好，这是Java的OD反应性
9 there exists a reactive streams API
9存在一个反应​​流API
currently in rector streams 1.0 this has
目前在导演流1.0中
everything you need to define the sort
定义排序所需的一切
of API between two different reactive
两个不同反应堆之间的API的数量
programming libraries
程式库
so obviously you have a publisher and
所以显然你有一个出版商
subscriber I don't want to talk too much
订户，我不想说太多
about what reacted streams really is or
关于什么是真正反应的流或
asynchronous programming or anything
异步编程或其他任何东西
like that
像那样
I just kind of want to skim over the
我只是想略过
surface of it and show you how it works
并向您展示其工作原理
in anger really and so with the reactor
真的很生气
streams API we have a publisher we have
流API我们有一个发布者
a subscriber we have a processor which
一个订户，我们有一个处理器
combines the publisher and subscriber
结合发布者和订阅者
and a subscription which kind of helps
和订阅有什么帮助
you to manage the relationship between
您来管理之间的关系
the publisher and subscriber
发布者和订阅者
implementations of reactive streams
反应流的实现
include things like echo streams reactor
包括回声流反应器之类的东西
rx Java vertex so a lot of these popular
rx Java顶点如此受欢迎
libraries for doing reactive programming
用于进行反应式编程的库
in Java and other jvm languages in fact
实际上在Java和其他jvm语言中
it's not just the jvm languages they
不只是他们的JVM语言
implement this API so that's quite nice
实现此API，所以非常不错
they can talk to each other without
他们可以互相交谈而无需
really caring about their own
真正关心自己
implementation that they're talking over
他们正在谈论的实现
the same API so for this reason in Java
相同的API，因此在Java中
9 we have got three active streams API
9我们有三个活动流API
built into the library and I think this
内置在图书馆里，我认为这
is a really positive thing I think this
我认为这是一件非常积极的事情
is great I think reactive streams and
我认为反应性流很棒，
reactive programming is a good model to
反应式编程是一个很好的模型
follow it's quite a nice way of doing
遵循，这是一个很好的方法
asynchronous programming it's not as
异步编程不是
complex as other models and the fact
与其他模型和事实一样复杂
that this comes as part of Java 9 I
这是Java 9 I的一部分
think means that we are kind of
认为意味着我们有点
embracing it as a Java community as a
作为一个Java社区来接受它
way one of the ways of working so this
工作方式之一，这样
is great the only downside is that of
很棒，唯一的缺点是
course the reactor streams API is
当然反应堆流的API是
actually different to the Java 9 API the
实际上与Java 9 API不同
API itself is not the interfaces are
API本身不是接口
called the same thing the methods are
方法被称为同一件事
called the same thing they have the same
他们称相同的东西
signatures but they're in a different
签名，但它们位于不同的位置
package so at the moment they're not
包装，所以目前他们还没有
really reusable so if I'm using rx Java
真正可重用，所以如果我使用rx Java
and I'm getting a publisher I'm getting
我正在找一个出版商
an org reactive streams publisher I'm
我是一个组织反应式流发布者
not getting a Java util concurrent flow
没有得到Java util并发流
publisher so that I'm for this
发布者，所以我为此
demonstration I actually wrote an
示范我实际上写了一个
adapter just to wrap those things and
适配器只是为了包装那些东西，
convert them from one to another but
将它们从一个转换为另一个
that's one of the things which I think
这是我认为的一件事
is is interesting to understand because
很有趣，因为
the libraries at the moment are going to
目前的图书馆将
be using the reactor streams API not the
使用反应堆流API而不是
Java 9 API obviously because they're not
Java 9 API显然是因为它们不是
compiling against Java 9 yet so when you
针对Java 9进行编译，因此当您
want to use something like a reactive
想要使用类似反应式的东西
API in my application I designed it to
我在应用程序中设计了API
be sort of event-driven so it seems like
是事件驱动的，所以看起来
quite a good fit for
非常适合
or directive API I I have really stupid
或指令API II确实很愚蠢
services they use WebSockets they take a
他们使用WebSockets的服务
string off a WebSocket and put a string
从WebSocket上串出一个字符串
onto the WebSocket and then I have
到WebSocket上，然后我有
obviously some business logic this
显然这是一些业务逻辑
basically is the architecture diagram
基本上是架构图
for everyone's application ever and but
永远为每个人的应用
I had some really simple business logic
我有一些非常简单的业务逻辑
because for a number of reasons one it
因为出于多种原因之一
needs to be an approachable
需要平易近人
understandable demo 2 I need to be
可以理解的演示2我需要
demonstrating Java 8 features so my
演示Java 8功能
business logic is generally speaking a
业务逻辑通常来说是
lambda expression which Maps the strings
映射字符串的lambda表达式
from one value to another so in the case
从一个值到另一个值
of the user service it takes a whole
整个用户服务
JSON representation of a tweet and
推文的JSON表示形式和
returns a username for example and so
返回一个用户名，例如，所以
this looks like you pass in the
看起来您通过了
signature is I'm going to take a
签名是我要带一个
function which is my business logic and
功能是我的业务逻辑，
an I to take advantage of that I pass in
我利用我传递的优势
a lambda expression or a method
Lambda表达式或方法
reference which represents the business
代表业务的参考
logic of my of my service
我服务的逻辑
so given this my services as you said
所以给你我所说的服务
are intentionally quite stupid but I can
故意很愚蠢，但我可以
make them a little bit smarter by
使他们变得更聪明
exposing the reactor streams API instead
公开反应堆流API
so what I sort of figured is that
所以我想的是
actually from a business logic point of
实际上是从业务逻辑的角度
view I could be listening or subscribing
我可能正在听或订阅
to a publisher which is going to give me
给要给我的出版商
a stream of messages and I can be as
信息流，我可以成为
sort of sending those messages to
将那些消息发送到
something which subscribes to me to a
使我订阅的东西
subscriber so I'm going to change the
订户，所以我要更改
shape of my overall service so that I
整体服务的形状，这样我
have a publisher which publishes strings
拥有一个发布字符串的发布者
in my case and a subscriber which
就我而言，还有一个订户
listens to the result of the of the
聆听的结果
business logic so oh yeah so let's take
业务逻辑，所以是的，让我们来
a quick look at what that looks like
快速浏览一下外观
so in the case let's go back to the
所以在这种情况下，让我们回到
diagram the publisher in my case is a
在我的情况下，发布者是一个
class called client endpoints because
该类称为客户端端点，因为
what that does is it listens to the
它的作用是听
WebSockets and then publishes some
WebSockets，然后发布一些
string value and so that's the that's
字符串值，那就是
client endpoints so what I need to do is
客户端点，所以我需要做的是
I just make client endpoint implement
我只是让客户端端点实现
float publisher and then what it needs
浮动发布者，然后它需要什么
to do once you implement float publisher
实现浮动发布程序后要做的事情
you need to implement subscribe and the
您需要实施订阅，
SUBSCRIBE method takes a subscriber and
SUBSCRIBE方法需要一个订户并
then you're going to do something so as
那么你将要做的是
a publisher what I care about is who is
我关心的发布者是谁
subscribed to me and then I will do
订阅我，然后我会做
something with those subscribers at a
与那些订户一起的东西
later date when I need to so I'm just
以后我需要的时候，我只是
going to manage those subscriptions by
将通过以下方式管理这些订阅
them by keeping them in a list so Java 9
通过将它们保存在列表中来实现它们，因此Java 9
provides the interfaces for the reactive
提供反应式的接口
streams API you don't need to implement
无需实现的流API
them with your own implementations the
他们与您自己的实现
idea is that you're going to use an
想法是，您将使用
implementation like rx Java or reactor
像rx Java或Reactor这样的实现
or something like that but for the case
或类似的东西，但对于这种情况
of my services because they're very very
我的服务，因为它们非常非常
stupid I actually decided to implement
愚蠢的我实际上决定实施
my own publisher so that's that's the
我自己的出版商，那就是
choice that I've made here but not
我在这里所做的选择，但不是
necessarily definitely not something I
一定不是我
would recommend and because there's
会建议，因为有
plenty of frameworks that do all this
可以完成所有这些工作的大量框架
stuff but I'm going to manage my own
东西，但我要自己管理
subscriptions from this point of view on
从这个角度来看
the other end the subscriber in my case
另一端是我的订户
is a class called broadcasting server
是称为广播服务器的类
endpoint and what that does is it
端点，它是做什么的
listens to stuff in the business logic
侦听业务逻辑中的内容
and then uses WebSockets to send that to
然后使用WebSockets将其发送到
whoever cares and so again what I've got
谁在乎，所以我又得到了什么
is I'm implementing subscriber and
我正在实施订户，并且
subscriber has unsubscribe on next on
订户已取消订阅
next is the interesting thing that's
接下来是有趣的事情
like what do I do when I'm given an
就像当我得到一个
event on error and on complete so those
事件发生在错误和完成时，
are the things that I have to implement
是我必须执行的事情
in my class so on subscribe' all I'm
在我的课上，所以订阅“我就是
going to do is I'm going to say give me
我要说的就是给我
everything that you get for the end of
结束时得到的一切
time what you can do if you want to as
时间，如果你想做的话
you say I only want to see the first
你说我只想看第一个
three messages but in my case I'm just
三个消息，但就我而言，我只是
going to always listen to what the
总是听什么
business logic sends me on next and what
业务逻辑让我知道接下来的事情
I need to do is I need to listen to all
我需要做的是我需要听所有
the sessions for all the sessions which
所有会话的会话
are listening to me and
在听我说
to send them that message on error may I
向他们发送错误消息
suggest that you do not do this error
建议您不要执行此错误
handling in asynchronous systems is a
异步系统中的处理是
very interesting situation and I did a
非常有趣的情况，我做了一个
lot of simple error handling in terms of
就以下方面而言，许多简单的错误处理
forgetting the demo working I did a lot
忘记了演示工作，我做了很多
of like print stacktrace and things like
像print stacktrace之类的东西
that and do not swallow errors in an
并且不要吞下错误
asynchronous system because things will
异步系统，因为事情会
just not work and you will have no idea
只是不工作，你将不知道
what to do about it
该怎么办
error handling is a first-class citizen
错误处理是一流的公民
of asynchronous systems and it's really
异步系统，这真的
important to understand what to do with
了解如何处理很重要
them and so don't do that and then do
他们，所以不要那样做，然后再做
something on complete so I need to close
东西完成了，所以我需要关闭
my WebSockets when when there's no more
我的WebSocket不再存在时
messages so it was fairly
消息，所以这是相当
straightforward for me to use the
对我来说，直接使用
reactive streams API to provide a simple
反应流API提供简单
API for anything that wants to and
适用于任何需要的API
basically create a new one of my
基本上创建了一个新的
services so what does that mean like how
服务，这意味着什么
am I going to use this API what's the
我要使用这个API是什么
point of having a reactive API and so
具有反应性API的观点
the first thing I'm going to look at is
我要看的第一件事是
I'm going to look at my tweet service
我要看一下我的推特服务
how can I now make use of a reactive
我现在如何利用反应式
programming framework in my tweet
我的推文中的编程框架
service how does that change things
服务如何改变事情
so what I had before and I've mentioned
所以我以前提到的
this a few times is that this was the
这几次是，这是
aim was to demo Landers and streams what
目的是演示着陆器并进行流式传输
I had before is I had this really nice
我以前有过我真的很好
feature of Java 8 why I use Files lines
Java 8的功能为什么我使用文件行
to get a stream of strings for for every
为每个人获取一串字符串
line in a file I will get a string back
文件中的一行，我将返回一个字符串
in a stream and then I can do something
在流中，然后我可以做点什么
with it so what I'm doing is I'm reading
有了它，所以我在读
I'm reading a file of tweets and then
我正在阅读推文文件，然后
for every line I'm just kind of omitting
每行我都略去了
that to anyone who cares I have to
对那些在乎我的人
filter out some noise in this file and
过滤掉此文件中的一些噪音，然后
then the other thing I do for the
然后我要做的另一件事是
purposes of the demo is that I insert a
该演示的目的是我插入一个
100 millisecond delay so that you can
100毫秒的延迟，以便您可以
see something interesting on the UI
在界面上看到有趣的东西
again do not do this in production but
再次不要在生产中这样做，但是
from my point of view as a demo
从我的演示角度来看
application this is actually part of my
应用程序，这实际上是我的一部分
business requirement you need to be able
您需要的业务需求
to see the tweets ticking over at a
看到推文在
regular interval so let's rewrite this
定期间隔，让我们重写一下
using reactor streams because we can so
使用反应堆流，因为我们可以
I'm going to use rx Java for this solo
我将为此使用Rx Java
album so that's adding rx Java I need to
专辑，所以我需要添加rx Java
add requires rx Java to my module info
添加需要rx Java到我的模块信息
because we're Java 9 now and then I'm
因为我们时不时是Java 9
going to say from iterable I don't get
从可怜我要说
to make the most as the nice files lot
充分利用好文件
lines features in in Java 8 but I do get
Java 8中的行功能，但我确实得到了
a chance to do something fairly similar
有机会做类似的事情
and then I can basically just lift the
然后我基本上可以解除
same functionality from here and add it
从这里添加相同的功能
onto my reactive streams the only
进入我的反应流
difference is there's no such a mess
区别在于没有这么乱
with it as peek so I use a method called
偷看它，所以我使用了一种称为
Duan next which does basically exactly
下段基本上做的准确
the same thing so I can use reactive
同样的事情，所以我可以使用反应
streams to do the same thing that I was
流做我曾经做过的同样的事情
doing with Java 8 streams we will
使用Java 8流，我们将
discuss the wisdom of this later so as
稍后再讨论这个智慧
you can see it looks more or less the
您可以看到它看起来或多或少
same I can just delete all of that we
同样，我可以删除所有这些
start my service
开始我的服务
and everything works the same way at
一切都以相同的方式
used to which is not a massive surprise
习惯这不是一个很大的惊喜
because the code looks almost exactly
因为代码看起来几乎完全一样
the same so you might be thinking to
一样，所以您可能会想
yourself well what's the point of that
你自己那是什么意思
now I've basically added another
现在我基本上已经添加了另一个
external library an external dependency
外部库外部依赖
to do exactly the same thing that I did
做和我完全一样的事情
before and I have slightly a slightly
之前，我有一点点
ugly a way of creating my streams well
很好地创建我的流的丑陋方法
react to streams gives you a bunch of
对信息流做出反应会给您很多
features you don't get with Java eight
Java 8所没有的功能
streams so for example this thing always
流，例如这个东西总是
made me quite uncomfortable this idea of
这个想法让我非常不舒服
like shoving in 100 millisecond pause
就像在100毫秒的暂停中推
especially using the peek method because
特别是使用偷看方法，因为
peek is just generally a sort of debug
窥视通常只是一种调试
method to allow you to do something on
允许您对某事做某事的方法
any many thing which comes through the
通过的任何很多东西
stream so this feels like a little bit
流，所以感觉有点像
of a hack
骇客
I'm with reactive streams you can do
我正在使用反应性流
things like you can create a flowable
像你可以创建一个流动的东西
for an interval so I can create a
间隔一段时间，以便我可以创建一个
flowable which is an interval of 100
间隔为100
milliseconds what this is going to do is
毫秒，这是要做的
let's call this tick this is going to
让我们称这为滴答
emit a long value every 100 milliseconds
每100毫秒发出一个长值
this is going to take over every 100
这将每100个接管一次
milliseconds so that's quite nice and
毫秒，这非常好，
then what I can do is I can merge that
那我能做的就是合并
with my stream or with my reactive
与我的流或与我的反应
stream for reading the file so I can I
流以读取文件，这样我就可以
can zip these two things together so
可以将这两件事拉在一起
that I can force this stream of reading
我可以强迫阅读
things from a file to admit things every
从文件中获取所有内容
100 milliseconds and this is fairly easy
100毫秒，这相当容易
I just have to say zip wiz give it the
我只需要说zip wiz给它
tick and then I have to tell it given
勾选，然后我必须告诉它
that I now have two values I have a long
我现在有两个值
value from the tick stream and I have a
滴答流的价值，我有一个
string value from my file reading stream
我的文件读取流中的字符串值
but I don't care about the long value
但我不在乎长期价值
because it's just a placeholder there to
因为它只是一个占位符
sort of take over so I'm going to just
接管，所以我要
omit the string value and then this way
省略字符串值，然后这样
I'll restart this I kind of I've used
我会重新使用
this feature from reactor streams which
反应堆流的这一特征
is the ability to actually work on two
是真正在两个方面工作的能力
streams and merge them together to give
流并将其合并在一起以给出
me something which does the same thing
我做同样的事情
as before but it's quite I think it's
和以前一样，但我认为确实是
quite a nice elegant solution to prove
一个很好的优雅的解决方案来证明
this is meant to happen it's meant to
这注定要发生，这意味着
take every hundred milliseconds rather
花费每一百毫秒
than using a slightly hacky approach
而不是使用稍微有点怪异的方法
so that's the feature of reactors dreams
这就是反应堆梦想的特征
you don't get with Java eight streams
Java 8流不具备
for example okay what else can we do
例如，好吧，我们还能做什么
I wonder the user service because it's
我想知道用户服务，因为它
not very interesting the mood service
心情服务不是很有趣
let's look at the mood service 13
让我们看看心情服务13
minutes left okay let's quickly look at
还剩几分钟，让我们快速看一下
the mood service
情绪服务
so here the what I did with the services
所以这是我对服务所做的
as you saw I am I exposed a publisher
如你所见，我是一位出版商
and subscriber to anything which is
和订户任何东西是
going to use these services and then I
要使用这些服务，然后我
just have to tell it what to do with
只是必须告诉它如何处理
those things so let's say I want to get
这些东西，所以说我想得到
moods with a publisher subscriber I'm
我与发布商订阅者的心情
going to use reactor to kind of show
打算用电抗器来展示
that you can use different
你可以使用不同的
implementations of vector streams this
向量流的实现
interviews in flowable I have flux flux
流动中的面试我有助焊剂
from publisher now I'm going to get an
现在我要从发布商那里得到一个
error here because from publisher is
错误在这里，因为来自发布者是
expecting a reactive streams publisher
期待一个被动的流发布者
and I'm passing it a flow table sure and
我肯定要通过它一张流程图
so I have an adapter to do that so
所以我有一个适配器来做到这一点
that's although I'm just going to wrap
那虽然我只是要包装
it inside my adapter and then what I can
它放在我的适配器中，然后我可以
do is I basically do the same thing I
我基本上是在做同样的事情
was doing with Java 8 streams I can do
我正在做的Java 8流
it with wreckfish streams flat maps of
它与残骸流平的地图
course is different because I can't take
当然不同，因为我不能接受
a stream I have to have a flux from
流，我必须从
array and then everything works exactly
数组，然后一切正常
the same way it did before which again
与之前一样
sort of begs the question what's the
有点问题是什么
point well the point is actually when oh
点好点，实际上是什么时候哦
yeah I need to
是的，我需要
I can't collect because I'm surprised
我无法收集，因为我很惊讶
that compiles I can't collect I need to
我无法收集的编译内容
subscribe I'm going to put the
订阅我要把
subscriber on to the end of that to
订户到最后
listen to that which also needs to be
听也需要
wrapped inside the adapter
包裹在适配器内
[Music]
[音乐]
so again this looks exactly the same as
所以再次看起来与
the Java eight streams what's the point
Java 8流有什么意义
the point is that actually if I run this
关键是实际上如果我运行
it doesn't work nothing happens he stops
它不起作用什么都没发生，他停了下来
and and this was this is a mystery
这是一个谜
especially as I'd overridden all of my
特别是当我覆盖了我所有的
error handling with I'll do something at
错误处理，我将在
this point and it turns out that that
这一点，事实证明，
reactor streams are an entirely
反应堆物流完全是
different model they work in entirely
他们完全可以工作的不同模式
different way they're designed to work
他们的工作方式不同
on infinite streams they're designed to
在无限流上，它们旨在
be combined the device design it's
结合设备设计
supposed to be split and they have the
应该分裂，他们有
idea of back pressure as a really
背压的想法
important first class citizen so with
重要的头等公民
with back pressure if your publisher
如果您的发布商背压
outpaces your consumer you have to
超过您的消费者，您必须
explicitly tell the system what to do
明确告诉系统该怎么做
about that are you going to drop
关于那你要放弃
messages on the floor are you going to
地板上的消息你要去吗
apply back pressure and force the
施加反压力并用力
producer the publisher to slow down so
制片人出版商放慢脚步
you have to understand how the flow of
您必须了解
information works through your system
信息通过您的系统起作用
and and if you don't things just fall
而且，如果你不做，事情就会倒下
over in this particular case it turns
在这种特殊情况下，它变成
out that flat map spawns off a whole
平面图产生了一个整体
bunch of different threads to deal with
一堆不同的线程来处理
flat map now this doesn't happen in Java
平面地图现在这在Java中不会发生
eight strings because if you're not
八弦，因为如果你不
going parallel it just says everything
并行它只是说了一切
in the single operation as a blocking
在单个操作中作为阻塞
single threaded operation and that's a
单线程操作，这是一个
completely different model to the
完全不同的模型
reactive streams thing so I had to put
反应流的东西，所以我不得不把
in a magic incantation to say only run
用魔咒说只能跑
that on one thread and then everything
一个线程，然后一切
works I would love to be able to give
我希望能够给予的作品
you some detailed information as to why
您为什么要提供一些详细的信息
that is but to be honest I don't know
那不过是说实话我不知道
but it works now and that's the
但现在可以了，那就是
important thing the well the important
重要的事情，重要的
message here is react Christians are not
这里的信息是反应基督徒不是
the same as Java eight streams Java
与Java八流Java相同
eight streams are a very nice way of
八个流是一个非常好的方法
querying collections in a way which is
查询集合的方式是
scalable if you use the magic parallel
如果使用魔术并行，则可扩展
incantation and your collection is big
咒语，你的收藏很大
enough and your operation is expensive
够了，您的手术很昂贵
enough you can spawn that over multiple
足够您可以生成多个
CPUs and that's good that's not the same
CPU，那很好，那是不一样的
model as reactive streams it's not for
建模为反应流，不是
doing the same thing even though the API
即使API也会做同样的事情
looks exactly the same it's very
看起来完全一样，非常
confusing all right so I've got nine
好吧，我已经九岁了
minutes to go over everything else
分钟以了解其他所有内容
really I'm not going to go into the
真的，我不会去
details of this because it's not that
这不是因为那的细节
exciting and
令人兴奋和
yes so reactors dreams look exactly the
是的，所以反应堆的梦想看起来像
same as job eight streams they are not
与工作八流一样，它们不是
the same every time you look at reactor
每次看反应堆都一样
streams you get this really intuitive
流，您将获得非常直观的
marble diagrams I don't really
我不是真的大理石图
understand that so you events that go on
了解这一点，以便您继续进行事件
one stream and events that go on another
一个流和继续发生的事件
stream streams don't cross don't cross
溪流不穿越，不穿越
the streams and you have no idea how
溪流，你不知道如何
they're supposed to interact with each
他们应该与每个人互动
other and which direction time goes in
其他以及哪个时间进入
but other than that it's a really clear
但除此之外，这非常清楚
way of explaining how reactive streams
解释反应流的方式
look right so reactor students work with
看起来不错，所以反应堆学生可以与
multiple streams you can have multiple
多个流可以有多个
consumers back pressure is really
消费者的背压真的是
important and they have a very different
重要，他们有很大的不同
concurrency model so if you are thinking
并发模型，因此，如果您在考虑
about going reactive and you have not
关于变得被动，你没有
already done so you need to understand
已经完成，所以您需要了解
these things otherwise things are going
这些东西，否则事情会发生
to go very confusing very quickly right
很快变得非常混乱
other Java 9 features good I've got a
Java 9的其他功能很好，我有一个
whole nine minutes to work on this
整个九分钟的时间
convenience factory methods for
便利工厂方法
collections has anyone heard of this a
收藏有人听说过
few people my personal opinion is that
几个人，我个人的看法是
this is going to be the most used
这将是最常用的
feature of Java 9 and it's a really
9的功能，这是一个真正的
silly one as well silly it's a really
一个愚蠢的人，一个愚蠢的人
useful one but it's a it's not as
有用的，但它不是
exciting as lambdas and strings let's
令人兴奋的lambda和字符串让我们
look at in the olden days ie now and you
看看过去，即现在和你
create let's make this a list okay it
创建，让我们将其列出来吧
makes a list of strings
列出字符串
and you'll create a list of strings by
然后您将通过创建一个字符串列表
doing something like arrays dot as list
做一些像数组点作为列表
so that's how we create little strings
这就是我们创建小字符串的方式
that's fine
没关系
in Java 9 you'll be able to say list of
在Java 9中，您可以说出
you just saved yourself something like
你只是救了自己像
four characters yay
四个字符
life is good and that's not super
生活是美好的，那不是超级
exciting it's kind of nice it looks a
令人兴奋的是，它看起来不错
bit better but what is kind of more
更好一点，但还有更多
interesting from my point of view is you
从我的角度来看，有趣的是你
can do the same thing with set but you
可以用set做同样的事情，但是你
could not do before so you can do this
以前做不到，所以你可以这样做
for creating in mutation unmodifiable
用于创建无法修改的突变
lists and unmodifiable sets of data so
列出和不可修改的数据集，因此
if you're going to set something up just
如果你要设置一些东西
once and then use it throughout your
一次，然后在整个过程中使用它
application so obviously I can see
应用程序，所以很明显我可以看到
there's being super useful for tests but
对于测试来说超级有用，但是
also this is production code here it was
这也是这里的生产代码
sort of test data but you quite often
某种测试数据，但您经常
might want to set up just a small
可能只想设置一个
collection that's going to be on
即将进行的收藏
modifiable and you want to do that as
可修改的，你想这样做
easily as possible so this is kind of
尽可能容易，所以这是一种
fine here
很好
where it's kind of more interesting from
从那里更有趣
my point of view is where we get look of
我的观点是
maps so again this isn't a false example
再次映射，这不是一个错误的例子
I put in here just to show Java 9 stuff
我在这里只是为了展示Java 9的东西
that I needed to do this in order to to
我需要这样做，以便
set up a static map with a set of values
用一组值建立一个静态映射
that I'm going to use to compare stuff
我将用来比较的东西
and so I have to have this horrible
所以我必须要有这个可怕的
static thing in here in order to set up
在这里设置静态东西
the map and it's horribly ugly but it's
地图，而且非常丑陋，但是
not uncommon we've have to do this a lot
不少见，我们必须要做很多
now we don't need to do this we can say
现在我们不需要这样做，我们可以说
map of entries
参赛地图
and so now we can do it with with maps
所以现在我们可以用地图做到这一点
of entries so that's kind of nice who
的条目，所以这是一个很好的人
saves ourselves some lines of code we
为自己节省了一些代码行
don't have to use an ASCII static block
不必使用ASCII静态块
and I can again I can see for some test
我可以再次看到一些测试
data this could be really useful
数据可能真的有用
it seems more useful if you have fewer
如果您更少的话，它似乎更有用
than ten entries because you don't need
超过十个条目，因为您不需要
hardly any of this you just say map of
您几乎不会说任何这样的地图
get rid of all of that
摆脱所有这些
and just two key value key value key
还有两个键值键值键
value for up to ten so given that I used
最多十个值
to work for MongoDB and most of my job
在MongoDB和我的大部分工作上工作
was writing maps inside Java this is
在Java中编写地图，这是
super useful and just gets rid of an
超级有用，只是摆脱了
awful lot of boilerplate around creating
围绕创建的大量样板
maps and other collection types so I
地图和其他收藏类型，所以我
think this is going to be extremely
认为这将是极端
valuable it's not quite as pretty as
有价值，不如
Groovy's way of doing it for example but
Groovy的方法例如
it is a good compromise compared to to
相比于
what we were doing before right five
我们在正确的五点之前做了什么
minutes left
还剩分钟
there will be no time for questions I do
我没有时间问问题了
apologize and right private methods on
道歉并主张私人方法
the interfaces now this might seem like
现在的接口看起来像
a really silly thing because interfaces
真的很愚蠢，因为界面
are supposed to define your public API
应该定义您的公共API
why would you need a private method on
你为什么需要一个私有方法
an interface well of course the answer
一个接口，当然答案
is that in Java 8 we got default methods
是在Java 8中我们有默认方法
and static methods on interfaces so for
接口上的静态方法，因此
example again this is some genuine code
再次示例，这是一些真正的代码
that was in this application and I have
那是在这个应用程序中，我有
static methods but I've got copy and
静态方法，但我有复制和
paste coding in here because there was
在这里粘贴代码，因为
no other elegant way of doing this I
我没有其他优雅的方式
mean I could extract this out into a
意味着我可以将其提取到一个
method get value for fields oops it's
方法获取字段的值哎呀
got value wrong and but this in Java 8
值错误，但这在Java 8中
this still has to be public and I might
这仍然必须公开，我可能
not have wanted to expose this on my API
不想在我的API上公开
of course now in Java 9 I just make that
当然，现在在Java 9中，我只是做到了
private and then I can reuse that code
私有的，然后我可以重用该代码
so that's going to be really useful if
因此，如果
you started using static or default
您开始使用静态或默认值
methods on your interfaces I'm sorry the
接口上的方法，对不起
spelling mistake is really killing me
拼写错误真的使我丧命
here feel better now and new methods on
现在感觉好多了，新方法
the streams API the Java eight streams
流API Java的八个流
API does allow you to work with infinite
API确实允许您使用无限
streams and that quite often doesn't let
流，并且通常不会让
you stop your infinite stream which
你停止了无限的流
seems like a tiny miscalculation
似乎是一个小小的错误估计
but now you have new methods on the
但是现在您有了新的方法
streams API to allow you to do some
流API，让您可以做一些
operation until something until
操作直到某事直到
something is true or to ignore a series
某些事情是正确的或忽略系列
of values until some operate until some
直到一些操作直到一些
value is true and it's called take while
值是真实的，这被称为
and drop while so for example and what I
并同时下降，例如，我
was using filter in this case because it
在这种情况下使用过滤器，因为它
kind of works I was trying to do
我试图做的那种工作
something for a certain set of values
有一定价值的东西
but now I can just say take while so
但是现在我只能说花点时间
while some criteria is true then I want
虽然一些标准是正确的，然后我想
you to do something and in this case my
你做点什么，在这种情况下我
stream is only 17 things long so it's
流只有17件事长，所以
not a big deal but obviously for things
没什么大不了的，但是很明显
like infinite streams you're going to
就像无限流一样
want to do something until some value
想做点事直到有价值
and then and then stop and this I did
然后停下来，我做了
get bitten by this before Java 9 came in
在Java 9出现之前就被这个咬了
because when I was reading my my file of
因为当我阅读我的档案时
tweets I had no way of terminating that
我没有办法终止
service just it's just going to go until
服务只是要去直到
the end of the file there's no way to
文件末尾没有办法
say stop now so this is gonna be really
说现在停止，这将是真的
useful so take while is do something
有用，所以花点时间做点什么
until some criteria and drop while is
直到一些标准，然后下降是
ignore everything until some criteria
忽略一切，直到有一些标准
and I believe you can combine the two so
我相信您可以将两者结合起来
you could say like in all all of these
你可以说所有这些
do something with these and then stop at
用这些做点什么，然后停在
this point it was particularly well on
这一点特别好
ordered streams but it doesn't have to
有序的流，但不必
be just ordered streams
只是被命令流
I'm the stat walking API had a play with
我是stat walk API玩过的
that this week because I thought I
这周是因为我以为我
should probably put some error handling
应该可能会进行一些错误处理
into my application and the stack
进入我的应用程序和堆栈
walking API let's have a look
步行API让我们看一下
I'll show you I haven't really played
我会告诉你我还没玩过
with it properly so do it bear with me a
正确地做，所以它承担我一个
bit though you can stack Walker and then
一点，虽然你可以堆叠沃克，然后
you can you couldn't walk your sacks you
你能不能走麻袋吗
give it some function and it gives you a
给它一些功能，它给你一个
stream and then you can do something so
流，然后你可以做些什么
a note that I'm not having to get the
我不需要得到的说明
stack trace from an error or anything I
错误或任何我的堆栈跟踪
can pick up my stack trace at any point
可以随时获取我的堆栈跟踪
in the application and what this lets me
在应用程序中，这让我做什么
do is I can do things like I can use the
我可以做的事情就是可以使用
power of streams to find for example
流的力量找到例如
let's say the first place in the stack
假设堆栈中的第一名
which has a particular package name or
具有特定的软件包名称或
how deep is my stack how deep is my step
我的堆栈有多深我的脚有多深
and how it start singing and or you know
以及它如何开始唱歌，或者你知道
you can do you can use the full power of
你可以做，你可以充分利用
the streams API to have a look at your
串流API看看您的
stack and of course the point here as
堆叠，当然这里的重点是
well as it's done lazily so because of
懒得做，是因为
course everyone knows stack traces are
当然每个人都知道堆栈跟踪是
really expensive if you if the stream
如果你的流真的很贵
operation is not applicable you're not
操作不适用，您不适用
you're not going to incur that cost so
你不会承担那笔费用，所以
this is quite nice I haven't had a
这很好，我还没有
chance to play with it like properly but
有机会像正常玩，但
I think this is going to be really
我认为这将是真的
useful under certain circumstances in
在某些情况下有用
particular I wanted to see where is the
特别是我想看看
first place in the stack where like my
像我一样在堆栈中排名第一
my package name might be available so or
我的包裹名称可能可用，或者
how many how deep is a bit where when my
多少深多少
packages are in there all my times up
我所有的时间都在打包
right nearly finished multi release jar
即将完成的多功能释放罐
files this is really exciting for me as
文件，这对我来说真的很令人兴奋
someone who works on library development
从事图书馆发展工作的人
stuff in the future from Java 9 onwards
从Java 9以后的未来
as a library developer I will be able to
作为图书馆开发人员，我将能够
release a jar file which makes use of
释放一个使用的jar文件
Java main functionality if you're using
Java主要功能（如果正在使用）
Java 9 otherwise makes use of pre Java 9
Java 9否则会使用Java 9之前的版本
functionality and and it will work for 9
功能，它将适用于9
and 10 and onwards or pre-job and I'll
10岁及以上，或工作前，我会
as far as I'm aware so for example I
据我所知，例如
don't know if this is going to happen rx
不知道这是否会发生
Java could for example release a single
例如，Java可以发布一个
jar file where it uses the Java 9
使用Java 9的jar文件
reactive streams API if you're using
如果您使用的是反应式流API
Java 9 otherwise it uses the reactor
Java 9否则将使用反应堆
streams API if you're not using Java 9
如果不使用Java 9，将使用流API
and I think this will be really useful
我认为这将非常有用
especially for migrating to Java 9 stuff
特别是对于迁移到Java 9的东西
process API updates you can now get the
处理API更新，您现在可以获取
pit of your process and kill it if you
坑你的过程，如果你杀死它
want to this is a good thing
想要这是一件好事
there's a bunch of other stuff in there
那里还有很多其他东西
as well so if you are like managing your
因此，如果您想管理自己的
own services if you're creating your own
自己的服务（如果您要创建自己的服务）
micro services you can do things like
微服务，您可以做类似的事情
actually use command line tools in a
实际使用命令行工具
really useful way updated application
真正有用的方式更新应用程序
you'll see this when you read the
当您阅读《
documentation you'll be able to see
您将能够看到的文档
whether a deprecated method is scheduled
是否计划了不推荐使用的方法
for deletion or whether it's just like I
删除还是像我一样
you probably shouldn't use this and
你可能不应该使用这个
you'll also see when something was
您还会看到什么时候
deprecated like Java 1.8 or 1.2 or
不推荐使用，例如Java 1.8或1.2或
whatever html5 Java dog if you generate
任何html5 Java狗（如果生成）
Java dot which most of us don't you can
Java点，我们大多数人不知道
generate it in html5 yeah Java Docs
在html5中生成它是的Java文档
search look look a little search bar in
搜索看起来有点搜索栏
Java dog skin brilliant the reptile
Java狗皮辉煌的爬行动物
thank God I don't have time to look at
谢谢上帝，我没有时间看
the reptile but there's a there's a
爬行动物，但是有一个
tutorial here I've talked about it in
我在这里讨论过的教程
some of my other talks as well and if
我的其他一些谈话以及
you are used to using a reptile and you
你习惯于使用爬行动物，而你
have ideas of how a rifle should work
对步枪应该如何工作有想法
inside an IDE please tell us because you
在IDE中请告诉我们，因为您
really want to understand what users
真的很想了解哪些用户
want from the repple right I'm sorry I'm
想要从乳头状权利对不起我
enormously over time I'm so sorry and
随着时间的流逝，我感到非常抱歉和
the pain of Java 9 your code might break
Java 9的痛苦可能会破坏您的代码
with Java 9 it's true your code might
使用Java 9确实是您的代码可能
break especially using Gradle and they
尤其是使用Gradle打破，他们
are working on it by the way they are
正在按照他们的方式进行
going to get it fixed and but at the
将其修复，但在
moment doesn't work but the best thing
片刻不起作用，但最好的事情
to do is just try it out as soon as
要做的就是尽快尝试
possible find out what the problems are
可能找出问题所在
especially if some of the problems
尤其是当某些问题
actually aren't your fault
其实不是你的错
and then someone else's fault you need
然后你需要别人的错
to be able to report it to those
可以向那些人报告
libraries or to the jdk team or so
库或jdk团队左右
whatever so please use it as soon as
不管怎样，请尽快使用它
possible and find out what the problems
可能找出问题所在
are and there's a bunch of stuff which
是，有一堆东西
is going away that's one of the reasons
消失这是原因之一
why stuff is going to break and there's
为什么东西会破裂，并且有
a bunch of stuff which is going to
一堆东​​西，这将
change for example g1 is now the default
更改，例如g1现在是默认值
garbage collector I don't think that's
垃圾收集器，我不认为那是
going to have a massive impact because I
将会产生巨大的影响，因为我
think if you care about what garbage
想想你是否在乎什么垃圾
collector you've already tuned it to
您已经将其调整到的收集器
within an inch of its life and if you
在生命的一英寸之内，如果
don't care about it it's probably not
不在乎它可能不是
going to make any difference things like
将产生任何变化，例如
all the new version strings version
所有新版本的字符串版本
string scheme it's now Java 9 notch over
字符串方案，现在是Java 9了
1.9 so if you're pausing the version
1.9所以如果您暂停版本
string to figure out whether you're
确定您是否在
running on one point eight one point six
一分八跑一分六跑
one point whatever and you're going to
一分一分，你将要
fall over when you pass Java 9 okay
当您通过Java 9时跌倒了
so be aware of that and other stuff Java
所以要注意Java和其他东西
9 is still evolving including IntelliJ
9包括IntelliJ仍在发展
IDEA so
想法如此
and these features are evolving and
这些功能正在发展，
things are getting better but it needs
情况正在好转，但需要
feedback some real developers to really
反馈一些真正的开发人员
help that happen you don't have to
帮助您不必发生这种情况
modularize your whole codebase in order
按顺序模块化整个代码库
to use Java 9 in fact if I I would
实际上，如果II将使用Java 9
recommend probably not doing that
建议可能不这样做
unless you absolutely have to and it
除非你绝对必须
might not it might not be for you it's
也许不是，也许不是你的
not it's a non-trivial thing to modular
不是模块化的重要内容
eyes your codebase but you don't have to
查看您的代码库，但不必
so don't panic about it is fine and
所以不要惊慌
reactors dreams are not the same as Java
反应堆的梦想与Java不同
8 streams so you have to be aware of
8个流，因此您必须要注意
what the different use cases are for
不同的用例有什么用
those things I found Java and I
我找到Java的那些东西
encourage encourages good design with
鼓励与
modularity encapsulation so on and so
模块化封装等等
forth so it just got me thinking a lot
来吧，这让我想了很多
more about architecture and design I
有关建筑和设计的更多信息
think this is a good thing
认为这是一件好事
encourages new ways of working with a
鼓励采用新的工作方式
rip-away the repple with reactive
用反应性撕开乳头
streams there are some different models
流有一些不同的模型
to use and there's lots of things in
使用，里面有很多东西
there that just make code nicer to write
那里只是使代码更易于编写
so things like the collections framework
像collections framework这样的东西
things like the stack walking API things
像栈行走API之类的东西
like the process API and all these
像流程API之类的
little bits and pieces just make it a
点点滴滴就变成了
little bit nicer to write code all the
更好地编写代码
resources for this talk are available at
有关此演讲的资源，请访问：
this link
这个连结
including slides links to more
包括幻灯片链接到更多
information links to all the stuff I use
信息链接到我使用的所有东西
to try and put this thing together and
尝试把这东西放在一起
when the video is available I will put
当视频可用时，我会放
it up on there as well too thank you
它也在那里谢谢你
very much
非常
[Applause]
[掌声]